I remember it made things worse.
I remember figures appeared, restraining her mother,
threatening the children, always demanding punishment.
I remember the attacks grew more violent
as the moving day approached.
I remember on the last night,
Kat and Sharon were told to leave the bedroom door open.
I remember Sharon refused the top bunk.
Finally, Kat gave in.
I remember the house was quiet.
I remember too quiet.
I remember then came the sound.
I remember a slimy, slithering noise
like something wet crawling across the floor.
I remember Sharon screamed.
I remember Kat froze.
I remember tentacle-like shapes
shot from under the bed,
wrapping around Sharon's ankles and wrists,
trying to drag her under.
I remember red eyes glowed from the darkness beneath.
I remember her sisters sat paralyzed, unable to move.