I've tried looking at the time, but every clock I look at is still frozen in place,
yet time still moves.
It's been dark outside far longer than it should be, at least I think it has.
I think what scares me the most is the fact that all doors and windows are still locked
and nailed shut.
As I said, I've searched all over.
Nothing, so where did those things go?
I'm not sure if this is some sort of trick or if they're hoping I'd gain a full sense
of optimism.
Unfortunately for them, as long as they still exist and I draw breath, they won't escape.
They took my wife from me, but they won't take anyone else.
The only place I haven't checked is the attic.