I remember old wood like something from the 1950s, worn with age.
I remember inside when necklaces, earrings and a photograph.
I remember a man in a grey suit and a woman with a forced smile stared back.
I remember the man's eyes.
They followed them.
I remember the same figure from their nightmares.
I remember their mother quickly closed it.
I remember eventually she sold it after moving.
My mother never understood what happened that last week.
I remember was it the house?
I remember the jewelry box.
I remember something else entirely.
I remember whatever it was she still checks under her bed.
I remember always.
I remember because you never know who would need punishment next.
If I ever tell this story again, it means I made it out.