I remember something in it wanted to punish them.
I remember from the moment they moved in, the house was alive.
I remember whispers echoed in the halls.
I remember windows tapped in the night.
I remember floors creaked.
I remember worst of all was the back room where Cat and Sharon slept.
A room their mother always called evil.
Sharon, 14 and rebellious fought constantly with their mother.
I remember the fights seemed to awaken something.
I remember at night Sharon would scream from nightmares, sometimes waking with scratches
and bruises.
I remember soon Cat, her mother and the other siblings began seeing things, shadows
that didn't belong, figures in corners, eyes that glowed in the dark.
I remember the house became a trap of fear and anger.
I remember her mother called a priest for a blessing.