I've neglected it till now, but if they're anywhere, then it'd be up there.
I've tried listening, nothing.
I know they hear me, so why not come down for me?
Should I be afraid?
I wonder why they're hiding up there.
Did they turn on the lights?
Are they the reason time is frozen yet accelerating?
Are they why it's dark outside?
Am I really believing myself?
I haven't laid eyes on these things, yet I'm acting as if I'd better them.
Maybe I am delusional, maybe this whole thing has been just delaying the inevitable.
Maybe I've completely lost my ever-loving mind.
I tried making food, but everything in my fridge was either spoiled, moldy, or growing something
unrecognizable.