I should have left sooner.
My mum still checks under the bed every night.
After hearing what happened in 1993, I understand why.
I remember Hale, my name is Ben,
and I want to tell you a story my mother cat used to tell me
whenever I misbehaved the story of what happened
to her sister, Sharon.
I remember cat swore it really happened.
I remember the older I get, the more I believe her.
I remember it was 1993 in rural New South Wales, Australia.
I remember cat was 12, living in an old house that looked nice,
but felt wrong.
I remember her family was about to move
because the house was no longer suitable,
or at least that's what her mother said.
I remember cats suspected the truth.
Her strict religious mother believed the house was evil.