I remember, and then she heard it, a voice, cold and cruel echoing in the room.
You will be punished, and you will join the jewellery in the box.
I remember you are a despicable human who deserves to be punished, cat screamed.
I remember the creature released Sharon disappearing before their mother ran in and turned
on the lights.
I remember, but the fear lingered.
I remember every shadow in the room felt alive.
I remember every corner seemed to watch.
I remember their mother led them outside to the car, but none of them slept that night.
I remember somewhere just outside the window the figure watched.
I remember the next morning as the beds were being taken down, their mother found something
under cat and Sharon's bed, a jewellery box.
I remember it hadn't been there before.