Not even the drinks I had were any good, as all were either flat, moldy, or thickened
into a goo that twitched if touched.
The only thing I found that was somewhat ingestible was some bottles of wine I had stored for
my wives and my date night.
That same night those things showed up in the night.
That same night I woke up to my wife, pale with a permanent scream face now rigged in place
forever, getting drunk wasn't exactly my plan, but I've got to drink something.
I'd receive hell from my wife in heaven if I were to die now, especially from dehydration.
Avenging her is my only reason for going on, and I intend on doing just that.
I hear something.
I was right.
They're up there.
I'll update again later.
I'm going to do some prepping.